whatsblog.com 2015-12-29

# Privacy | Whatsblog

This Privacy Policy will describe Whatsblog policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information. Whatsblog receives your information through our website. When using any of our Services you openly consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Your information may be used in any country in which Whatsblog operates.

## Collection of information and use

Whatsblog collects and uses your information to provide our Services. Information Collected When You Join: When you create a profile at Whatsblog you will provide some basic information such as your name, username, password, and email address. Some information such as name and username will be displayed publicly on Whatsblog.

Additional Information: You may provide Whatsblog with additional information that can be made public. This information can product information, description, and a picture. Whatsblog may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe from these messages by following the instructions contained within the messages or the instructions on the Whatsblog web site. If you email Whatsblog, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is optional.

Data Log: The Whatsblog servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms.

Facebook: When connecting to facebook using fconnect we will ask for certain information about you that can be used identify the ownership of your facebook page. Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your full name, your facebook page url and your facebook page likes. We keep your entire information private except the total number of likes which is displayed to brands who you have voluntarily applied for their promotion.

## Disclosure of Information Sharing

Whatsblog does not ever disclose your private information except for the circumstances listed here.

You Give Consent: Whatsblog may share information when your consent is given, such as a third party client accessing your Whatsblog profile.

Service Providers: Whatsblog uses some trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us. We may share your personal information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services.

Law and Harm: Whatsblog may disclose your information if we must legally comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect Whatsblog's rights or property.

Business Transfers: In the event that Whatsblog is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this privacy policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new ownership.

Non-Private or Non-Personal Information: Whatsblog may share your non-personal information such as promotion campaigns you have taken part in or how many clicks your campaign link received.

## Changes to this Policy

Whatsblog may revise this Privacy Policy as needed. Your continued use of Whatsblog after those changes become effective, is an agreement to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
